# Sarah Barrett

Email: barrett.sarahk@gmail.com | Location: Lehi, UT 84043 | Phone: 253 326 7916

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/sarahkathrynbarrett/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/sarahkathrynbarrett/</a>
Portfolio: <a href="https://sarahkathrynbarrett.myportfolio.com/">https://sarahkathrynbarrett.myportfolio.com/</a>

#### **Summary**

Tech-savvy UX/UI Designer with a background in front-end web design and development, specializing in creating user-friendly design that is also stunning. Proven background in graphic design, social media marketing and management, search engine optimization, photography, and editing.

#### **Technical Skills**

HTML, CSS, User Experience, UI Grids and Composition, Color Theory, Interaction Design, Typography, Heuristic Evaluation, Photography, Social Media, Marketing, SEO, User Research, Interviewing, Graphic Design, Information Architecture, and Guerilla Testing

### **Projects**

<u>Local Support App</u> ◆ NASA Homepage Redesign ◆ <u>Everyday Travel App</u>

## **Work Experience**

Cove Smart - Orem, Utah

October 2020 - present

Customer Service Agent

- Achieved the highest Quality Assurance score during first week out of training
- Worked with customers daily and provided top tier customer service
- Developed interactive interface for new agent training purposes

Vivint Smart Home - Provo, Utah

October 2019 - June 2020

Customer Loyalty Representative

- Performed excellent spoken communication skills with frustrated customers
- Rose to top retention performer on my team
- Worked with leadership to get promotion in a competitive environment
- Handled multiple tasks throughout the day, working under pressure

Brigham Young University - Rexburg, Idaho

January 2019 - April 2019

Business Management Office Assistant

- Assisted in grading coursework for the Social Media Marketing course
- Answered questions regarding the business department, including marketing
- Asked to design the website for the Marketing department
- Assisted the entire Business department during my final and most challenging semester

DeafandHoH LLC - remote

September 2018 - January 2019

## Web Design Intern

- Assisted in the company rebranding and design
- Helped develop code for the new Wordpress site
- Created company emails using Mailchimp

• Took data from spreadsheets and used HTML and CSS to display it on the website

Brigham Young University - Rexburg, Idaho

April 2018 - August 2018

Teacher's Assistant

- Assisted the class B320: Advanced Writing in Professional Contexts
- Graded all coursework led one lesson
- Worked individually with students who needed help and tutored when needed
- Worked with the professor on a weekly basis to stay up to date

## Education

Certificate in UX/UI February 2021 University of Utah

Bachelors of Science, Web Design & Development Brigham Young University-Idaho April 2019